Guide to the Kembra Pfahler Papers MSS.425
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II. Personal and Project Files, 1961-2015; 8.25 Linear Feet in 8 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 oversize flat box, 1 small flat box, 1 flat-file folder, 4 folders in a shared manuscript box, and 2 oversized folders in shared boxes
  - Filmmaking -- Poster for Pfahler Event at Anthology Film Archives, 2000 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Filmmaking -- Unknown Movie with The Girls of the Voluptuous Horror of Karen Black in Bunk Beds -- Film Stills, circa 1989-2000s (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Filmmaking -- Film Still by Annie Sprinkle of Pfahler Performing, circa 1989-2000s (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Press Clippings, 1984-2007, 2014 (Box 15, Folder 1, Box 19, Folder 2, Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Artwork -- Sketch by Samoa, 1986 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Nick Zedd Drawings of Pfahler, 1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Resume and Business Cards, circa 1989, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Modeling -- Editorial Images, 1991-2007 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Laure Leber, 1992, 2001, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Katrina del Mar, 1995, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Richard Kern, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Modeling -- Posed Images of Pfahler (Some Self-Portrait), 1997, undated (Box 15, Folder 8, Box 20, Folder 11, Box Shared Fales 109, Folder 2)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Ward Boult, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Modeling -- Photo Shoot with Pfahler, Nick Zedd, and Annie Sprinkle, circa 1999 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Rosalie Knox, 2001, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Modeling -- Photo Shoot for Vogue Magazine with Pfahler, Rick Owens, and Annie Liebowitz, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Modeling -- Photo Shoot with Pfahler as Karen Black with Ducati Motorcycle, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Modeling -- Photo Shoot with Pfahler as Karen Black Character with Cats, circa 1989-2000s (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Modeling -- Photographs by Kris Fernald, circa 1989-2000s (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Notes, Writing Scraps, Partial Journal Entries, 1994, undated (Box 16, Folder 3-9)
  - Exhibitions and Related Events -- Kembra Pfahler: Availabism and Anti-Naturalism: A Feminine Experiment and Live Performance of A Star is Born: The Horror Version -- Photographs, Press Clippings, Promotional Material, March-April 2003 (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
  - Exhibition Announcements, 2004-2008 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Exhibitions and Related Events -- The Voluptuous Horror of Karen Black, Work by Kembra Pfahler in Collaboration with Ned Ambler and Scott Ewalt -- Price Sheets with Artwork Images, February 2006 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Exhibitions -- Womanizer -- Promotional Mailers, Invitations, Catalog, Photographs, Notes, January 2008 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Exhibitions -- Giverny with E.V. Day and Kembra Pfahler -- Promotional Packet, Notes, Promotional Announcement, March-April 2012 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Candy Coated Evil -- Designs by Samoa -- Photographs from Event, Press Clippings, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Punk Ladies of Wrestling (PLOW) Event / Movie -- Press Release, Event Photographs, Movie Promotional Material, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Colin de Land -- Memorial Events Announcements, 2003, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Fashion Design -- Pfahler's Drawings, Magazine Fashion Editorial, Notes, Label Sample, Logo, Press Clippings, Photographs from Runway Shows, 2003-2004 (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
  - "First Aid for Choking" State of New York Poster Using Women of Karen Black Band Images, circa 2007-2008 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Exhibition Catalog for Joe Coleman: Auto-Portrait Containing Pfahler's Image, 2010 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Artwork Images, Undated, circa 1980s-1999 (Box 17, Folder 3, Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Teaching -- Performance Art 101 -- Lecture Notes, Agreement, undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Event Promotional Material, undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Event with Pfahler and Women of Black Karen Band, undated (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Event Photographs by Ward Boult -- Pfahler Signing Books and Preparing for Performance, undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Pfahler-Hosted Event -- Photographs, undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Event Photographs -- Pfahler Performing as Karen Black Character, undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Photograph-Decorated Box -- Gifted from Friend Peter, undated (Box 18, Folder 6)